us.jobs 2019-01-01

# Jobs Hiring Now | us.jobs

**Employ Media, LLC ("EM") recognizes that visitors and users this website (the "Website") value their privacy. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of information about our users collected on the Website. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to theTerms and Conditions of Use applicable to the Website. By using this Website, you consent to all terms contained in this Privacy Policy.**

### 1\. The Information EM Collects

User Provided Information: You may provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your resume/CV, your name, email address, payment information, contact information and other information required to create and manage your account) to EM when choosing to participate in various services or activities on the Website. You may also provide additional content while participating in various services or activities on the Website.   
Cookies Information: When you visit the Website, we may send one or more cookies – a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. EM may also use session cookies. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Website may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. Please note that this information applies to the use of cookies by EM and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technology by any third parties.   
Log File Information: When you use the Website, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

### 2\. The Way EM Uses Information

If you submit personally identifiable information or other user-provided information to us through the Website, then we may use such information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Website, including, when applicable, sending you information.   
Any information or content that you voluntarily disclose for public posting to the Website may become available to the public and may be accessed, used and stored by others around the world. Accordingly, you should not post sensitive personal information or any other information that you would not want made public. You should never provide your social security number, national insurance number, financial information, passport number, and other sensitive information.   
We may use cookies and log file information to: (a) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; and (b) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc. 

### 3\. When EM Discloses Information

We may release information we collect, including personally identifiable information and other user-provided information, if required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant.   
We also reserve the right to disclose information we collect, including personally identifiable information and other user-provided information, that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use; take precautions against liability; investigate and defend EM against any third party claims or allegations; assist government enforcement agencies; protect the security or integrity of our Website; and protect the rights, property, or personal safety of EM, our users or others.   
We may also disclose the information we collect, including personally identifiable information and other user-provided information, with any EM subsidiaries or affiliates, vendors, sponsors, promoters, advertisers or other selected third party providers of services. We may also authorize third party vendors to collect such information on EM’s behalf. We will disclose such information to third parties to fulfill the purpose for which you provided it, such as sending your resume to prospective employers or forwarding your contact information to social connects. 

### 4\. Special Note to International Users

The Website is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to users in the United States. If you are accessing the Website from any country outside the U.S., please be advised that through your continued use of the Website, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and our Terms and Conditions of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. 

### 5\. Service Providers

We use a credit card processing company to bill users for services. Credit card information that you or authorized persons provide when you make any payment by credit card via this Website will only be used to process the transaction(s) you request. The credit card processing company will not otherwise retain, share, or store any credit card information provided during payment. If you would like to know more about privacy policies of our credit card processing company, you may e-mail us at [legal@find.jobs](mailto:legal@find.jobs). 

### 6\. Security

EM uses industry standard efforts to make sure all information received from online visitors is secure from unauthorized access and use. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place the appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information collected.   
You should keep in mind, however, that no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure and any information disclosed online can potentially be collected and used by parties other than the intended recipient. 

### 7\. Opt-Out Policy

If you do not wish to receive EM's promotional communications that are sent via e-mail, you will always have the opportunity to "unsubscribe" from receiving such communications.

### 8\. Links to Third-Party Websites

This Website may contain advertising or other links to third-party websites. EM does not control these third-party websites or their information collection practices. EM will not be responsible for the activities of these third parties. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave the Website and to read the privacy statements of any third-party website.

### 9\. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy

EM may change or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. Any change or amendment will be effective immediately upon posting to this Website. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes or amendments to this Privacy Policy.

### 10\. Contact Information

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you can contact EM at: [legal@find.jobs](mailto:legal@find.jobs).
